

#### Personal

#### Name

Priyadarshini Rajmohan

# Address

D-F2, Sudarshan Urban Ville, Thanthai Periyar St, Cholavaram Nagar, Nagalkeni, Chrompet 600044 Chennai

Phone number 9524277129

#### **Email**

priyasathyasai@gmail.com

#### Website

https://priyadarshinisai.github.io/Priya

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/priyadarshinirajmohan-b26b23b0

#### **Interests**

**Painting** 

Cooking

**Playing Badminton** 

# Priyadarshini Rajmohan

Passionate person with skills in IT. Worked in web based application projects and provided technical support to end-users, leveraging broad based expertise to handle problem identification .

About 3+ years of experience in JAVA, Spring and SQL and in front end technologies like Angular, HTML5, CSS3 , bootstrap. Looking forward to work with leading software companies to give my complete contribution with my experience for active participation and to lead the team, meeting the target on time and achieving success for walk of my life and for the company.

# Work experience

# **Technology Analyst**

Jul 2021 - Present

Infosys, Chennai

- Developing software programs meeting both technical and consumer needs.
- Developing APIs and designing user interactions on web pages.
- Always challenge current situation and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality
- Working with team for better delivery of programs.
- Hold team meetings to manage expectations and make team changes.
- Carrying out proper unit testing and integration testing using Karma.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing down time.
- Resolving technical issues.
- Worked on screen conversions and new screens in Ford Recall Management as Full Stack Developer.

# **Senior System Engineer**

Jul 2020 - Jun 2021

Infosys, Chennai

- Worked effectively to deliver software programs of the functionalities/requirements as expected on time with code quality.
- Always challenge current situation and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality
- Collaborating with team for better delivery of programs.
- Performing proper unit testing and integration testing using Karma.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing down time.
- Resolving technical issues.
- Worked on screen conversions and new screens in Ford Recall Management as Full Stack Developer

### **System Engineer**

Jul 2018 - Jul 2020

Infosys, Chennai

- Deliver software programs on time.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality
- Collaborating with team for better delivery of programs
- Always challenge situations and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing proper unit testing and integration testing using Karma.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing down time.
- Performed automation process to reduce work time and to process data more effectively.
- Monitoring, recoding and responding to request for support.
- Worked on screen conversion and new screens in Toyota Financial service and Ford for single global system as Full Stack Developer

### **System Engineer Trainee**

Jan 2018 - May 2018

Infosys, Mysore

- Trained in JAVA ,Angular and bootstrap.
- Developed Blog search engine for sports category with quick response.
- Performing Analysis and completing the project on time with quality.

# **Education and Qualifications**

# **B.E (Computer Science and Engineering)**

Kongu Engineering College, Perundurai

Graduated with 92% CGPA with First class designation

Jun 2014 - Apr 2018

# **Strength and Weakness**

Strength: Dedicated, Creative, Focused

Weakness: Detail Oriented

# **Skills**

Programming skills

Team lead

Problem Solving

Analytical Ability

Perseverance

Collaboration

Critical Thinking

# **Technical Expertise**

Technologies: JAVA/J2EE,Spring,RDBMS

Web Technologies: Angular 8, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3

**Testing Tool:** Karma **Version Control:**Git

## **Achievements**

Awarded for being flexible and dedicated resource. For gaining the customer confidence in short span of time and also for coming up with automation idea and developed the tool to automate the reports which saves monthly 12 hours of manual effort.

# Certifications

• Infosys Global Agile Developer Certification

## **Courses**

Angular Progressive Web Apps	Nov 2021 - Nov 2021

Udemy

# Go Java Full Stack with Spring Boot and Angular Apr 2021 - Apr 2021

Udemy

# Developing presentation layer and web services of Enterprise application using spring

Infosys Internal Course

# Getting started with Angular

Infosys Internal Course

Jun 2020 - Jun 2020

Nov 2019 - Nov 2019